{
    "categories": [],
    "description": "US State Capitals",
    "difficulty": -1,
    "questions": [{
        "answer": "Sacramento",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "California"
    }, {
        "answer": "Denver",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Colorado"
    }, {
        "answer": "Honolulu",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Hawaii"
    }, {
        "answer": "Phoenix",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Arizona"
    }, {
        "answer": "Atlanta",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Georgia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Boston",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Massachusetts"
    }, {
        "answer": "Tallahassee",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Florida"
    }, {
        "answer": "Austin",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Texas"
    }, {
        "answer": "Juneau",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Alaska"
    }, {
        "answer": "Little Rock",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Arkansas"
    }, {
        "answer": "Indianapolis",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Indiana"
    }, {
        "answer": "Albany",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "New York"
    }, {
        "answer": "Boise",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Idaho"
    }, {
        "answer": "Oklahoma City",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Oklahoma"
    }, {
        "answer": "Salt Lake City",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Utah"
    }, {
        "answer": "Dover",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Delaware"
    }, {
        "answer": "Baton Rouge",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Louisiana"
    }, {
        "answer": "Montgomery",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Alabama"
    }, {
        "answer": "Springfield",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Illinois"
    }, {
        "answer": "Nashville",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Tennessee"
    }, {
        "answer": "Hartford",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Connecticut"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jackson",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Mississippi"
    }, {
        "answer": "Columbus",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Ohio"
    }, {
        "answer": "Des Moines",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Iowa"
    }, {
        "answer": "Topeka",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kansas"
    }, {
        "answer": "Saint Paul",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Minnesota"
    }, {
        "answer": "Carson City",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Nevada"
    }, {
        "answer": "Santa Fe",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "New Mexico"
    }, {
        "answer": "Salem",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Oregon"
    }, {
        "answer": "Augusta",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Maine"
    }, {
        "answer": "Frankfort",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Kentucky"
    }, {
        "answer": "Annapolis",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Maryland"
    }, {
        "answer": "Helena",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Montana"
    }, {
        "answer": "Trenton",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "New Jersey"
    }, {
        "answer": "Raleigh",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "North Carolina"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lansing",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Michigan"
    }, {
        "answer": "Providence",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Rhode Island"
    }, {
        "answer": "Olympia",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Washington"
    }, {
        "answer": "Lincoln",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Nebraska"
    }, {
        "answer": "Bismarck",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "North Dakota"
    }, {
        "answer": "Richmond",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Virginia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Harrisburg",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Pennsylvania"
    }, {
        "answer": "Cheyenne",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Wyoming"
    }, {
        "answer": "Columbia",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "South Carolina"
    }, {
        "answer": "Pierre",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "South Dakota"
    }, {
        "answer": "Madison",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Wisconsin"
    }, {
        "answer": "Charleston",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "West Virginia"
    }, {
        "answer": "Jefferson City",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Missouri"
    }, {
        "answer": "Montpelier",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "Vermont"
    }, {
        "answer": "Concord",
        "category": "US State Capitals Quiz",
        "question": "New Hampshire"
    }],
    "quizLength": 50,
    "title": "US State Capitals Quiz",
    "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/name-state-capitals.php"
}